[
  {
    "question": "What is behind the blanks in 'be - was - ....'?",
    "choice1": "is",
    "choice2": "were",
    "choice3": "am",
    "choice4": "been",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which form is correct for 'begin - began - ....'?",
    "choice1": "beginned",
    "choice2": "begun",
    "choice3": "beganed",
    "choice4": "begined",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Find the correct form for 'forget - forgot - ....'?",
    "choice1": "forgotten",
    "choice2": "forgets",
    "choice3": "forgetted",
    "choice4": "forgoten",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete 'do - did - ....'?",
    "choice1": "done",
    "choice2": "did",
    "choice3": "doed",
    "choice4": "do",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "The correct form for 'eat - ate - ....' is?",
    "choice1": "eat",
    "choice2": "eated",
    "choice3": "eated",
    "choice4": "eaten",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is in the blanks for 'go - went - ....'?",
    "choice1": "gone",
    "choice2": "goed",
    "choice3": "going",
    "choice4": "went",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Find the correct form for 'have - had - ....'?",
    "choice1": "has",
    "choice2": "have",
    "choice3": "had",
    "choice4": "having",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete 'see - saw - ....'?",
    "choice1": "see",
    "choice2": "seen",
    "choice3": "sawed",
    "choice4": "saw",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "The correct form for 'take - took - ....' is?",
    "choice1": "taken",
    "choice2": "take",
    "choice3": "took",
    "choice4": "taking",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which form is correct for 'write - wrote - ....'?",
    "choice1": "written",
    "choice2": "write",
    "choice3": "wroted",
    "choice4": "wrote",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank : How _______ does this cost? ",
    "choice1": "many",
    "choice2": "far",
    "choice3": "much",
    "choice4": "long",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank : I am so ____________. I need to eat something. ",
    "choice1": "thirsty",
    "choice2": "exhausted",
    "choice3": "much",
    "choice4": "hungry",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank : London is the capital of the United ________ . ",
    "choice1": "country",
    "choice2": "Kingdom",
    "choice3": "land",
    "choice4": "States",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank : No way?! It’s already 8pm?! ___________. ",
    "choice1": "time flies",
    "choice2": "time goes",
    "choice3": "times flies",
    "choice4": "time escapes",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank : _________________ you give me a hand, please? ",
    "choice1": "will",
    "choice2": "do",
    "choice3": "could",
    "choice4": "shall",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank : He is ____________ travelling throughout Asia. ",
    "choice1": "right now",
    "choice2": "actually",
    "choice3": "currently",
    "choice4": "promptly",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank : Yesterday, I was so upset that  I __________  sleep… ",
    "choice1": "wouldn't",
    "choice2": "couldn't",
    "choice3": "shouldn't",
    "choice4": "can't",
    "answer": 2
  }
]
